# Daniel Cannon Smith

281.391.9630 Houston.TX (Willing to relocate.)

Email: dancannon27@icloud.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dancannon27/Github: https://github.com/Dancannon27

A Junior Web Developer that has served in the US Navy for six years, supported operation Enduring Freedom and supported operations involving protecting nuclear weapons at sea. After military separation I pursued the entertainment industry for sound design for video and video games. While earning that degree I delivered for a food service website and operated dispatch via web application. Today I am a school bus driver looking to find a more challenging career as a web developer

#### Skills & Tools:

### **Web Development**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Responsive Design, Bootstrap, Handlebars, Cookies/Local Storage, React.js, Node.js, Express, Security and Session Storage, User Authentication, MySQL, MongoDB

Advanced skills using the following Audio and Video editing software: Pro Tools, Logic Pro, Final Cut Pro

## Work Experience:

School Bus Driver – Katy I.S.D. – Katy, TX 281.396.7560 (Supervisor: Kale McKisson) November 2016 – Present

Delivery Driver/Dispatcher –
Bringittome.com – San Diego, CA 619.821.8182 (Owner: Sherry Nep)
August 2014 – April 2016

Steam Turbine Mechanic/Nuclear Weapons Security Guard – US Navy (DD-214 upon request) April 2004 – April 2010

#### Education:

University of Texas-Austin Certificate in Web Development – Grad: 03/24/18

The Art Institute of California- San Diego
Bachelor of Science in Audio Production – Grad: 03/24/16